Guide to the Rupert G. Miller Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Analysis of Variance II, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Analysis of Variance III, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Analysis of Variance IV, 1966-1967 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Statistics 122 I (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Statistics 122 II (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Statistics 122 III (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Statistics 124 I (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Statistics 124 II (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Statistics 124 III (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Design of Experiments: 1963 (1) (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Design of Experiments: 1963 (2) (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Statistics 605: Advanced Probability I, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Statistics 605: Advanced Probability II, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Statistics 605-606: Advanced Probability III, 1963-1964 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Statistics 606: Advanced Probability IV, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Statistics 606: Advanced Probability V, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Statistics 606: Advanced Probability VI, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Statistics 230C: Advanced Probability I (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Statistics 230C: Advanced Probability II (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Statistics 230C: Advanced Probability III (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Statistics 230C: Advanced Probability IV (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Statistics 217-218 I, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Statistics 217-218 II, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Statistics 217-218 III, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Statistics 217-218 IV, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes I, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes II, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes III, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes (1975-1976) I (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes (1975-1976) II (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Statistics 217-218: Stochastic Processes (1975-1976) III (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Introduction to Stochastic Processes I, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Introduction to Stochastic Processes II, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Introduction to Stochastic Processes III, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Applied Probablity Notebook I, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Applied Probablity Notebook II, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Applied Probablity Notebook III, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Applied Probablity Notebook IV, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Applied Probablity Notebook V, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Statistics 60 Notebook I (Fall 1984) (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Statistics 60 Notebook I (Spring 1983) (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Statistics 60 Notebook II (Spring 1983) (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Statistics 60 Notebook III (Spring 1983) (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Statistics 40: Chance and Strategy Notebook I (Autumn 1980) (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Statistics 40: Chance and Strategy Notebook II (Autumn 1980) (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Statistics 40: Introduction to Probability Notebook I (Autumn 1977) (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Statistics 40: Introduction to Probability Notebook II (Autumn 1977) (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Statistics 116 Notebook (Spring 1970) (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Statistics 116 Notebook (1962) (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Statistics 116: I Notebook (1959) (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Statistics 116: II Notebook (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Statistics 116: III Notebook (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Statistics 116: IV Notebook (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Statistics 60: I Notebook (Autumn 1978) (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Statistics 60: II Notebook (Autumn 1978) (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Statistics 10 Notebook (Spring 1975) (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Statistics 110 Notebook, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Statistics 236A Notebook I, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Statistics 236A Notebook II, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Statistics 136 Notebook I, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Statistics 50 Notebook I (1962) (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Statistics 50 Notebook II (1962) (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Statistics 50 Notebook I (1961) (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Statistics 280A: Analysis of Variance Notebook I, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Statistics 280A: Analysis of Variance Notebook II, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Statistics 280A: Analysis of Variance Notebook III, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Analysis of Variance: Appendix IV (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Statistics 261: Design and Analysis of Experiments Notebook I (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Statistics 261: Design and Analysis of Experiments Notebook II (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Statistics 261: Design and Analysis of Experiments Notebook III (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Statistics 202A: Probability and Statistics Notebook I (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Statistics 202A: Probability and Statistics Notebook II (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Statistics 202A: Probability and Statistics Notebook III (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Statistics 202A: Probability and Statistics Notebook IV (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Statistics 202B: Probability and Statistics Notebook I (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Statistics 202B: Probability and Statistics Notebook II (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Statistics 202B: Probability and Statistics Notebook III (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Statistics 202B: Probability and Statistics Notebook IV (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Statistics 202B: Probability and Statistics Notebook V (Box 39, Folder 7)
- "Calculus of Variations" Notes from lectures by D. Gilbarg (Box 39, Folder 8)
- "Theory of Games" (STAT 236a) Final Examination and Notes, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- "Advanced Complex Variables / Transform Theory" Notes, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- "Topics in Stochasitc Processes" Notes, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- "Advanced Probability" Notes from lectures by Henry Teicher (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Queueing Processes Notebook (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Statistics 233: Applied Statistics Notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- "Theory of Estimation" Lectures by E. L. Lehman, Notes by Colin Blyth, 1949-1950 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Untitled Notebook [mostly on sampling] (Box 40, Folder 2)
- "Analysis of Variance" Notes from lectures by Charles Stein (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Math 319: Interpolation by Rational Functions, notes, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Math 309: Design of Experiments Term Paper, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- "Theory of Games" I, Lectures by Sam Karlin, Notes by R.G. Miller (Box 40, Folder 6)
- "Theory of Games" II, Lectures by Sam Karlin, Notes by R.G. Miller (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Math 279: Genetics, lectures by S. Karlin, 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Math 313: The Riemann Surface [notes from lectures or possibly sources on the topic] (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Examples of Quick and Easy Comparisons [notes from lectures or possibly sources on the topic] (Box 41, Folder 3)
- "Linear Spaces" Notes (Box 41, Folder 4)
- "Theory of Testing Hypotheses" lectures by E. L. Lehman, Notes by Colin Blyth (Box 41, Folder 5)
- "Applied Multivariate Analysis" Notes (Box 41, Folder 6)
- "Functions of a Real Variable" by H. L. Royden, CH. 1-3 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- "Functions of a Real Variable" by H. L. Royden, CH. 4-7 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- "Functions of a Real Variable" by H. L. Royden, CH. 9-11 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- "Lectures on the Analysis of Variance" by Henry Scheffe, 1956 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- "Data Analysis, Including Statistics by Frederick Mosteller and John W. Tukey, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Asst. Prof. Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Assistant Professor Committee, 1965-66 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Assistant Professor Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Asst. Prof. Search Committee (1), 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Asst. Prof. Search Committee (2), 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Authorized Courses for B.S. (old) (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Authorized Courses for B.S. (new), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Undergraduate Study Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Elementary Course Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Undergraduate Program Report, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Committees and Minutes I, 1961-1962 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Committees, 1962-1963 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Committees and Minutes II, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Faculty Meetings I, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Faculty Meetings II, 1966-1967 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Faculty Meetings III, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Faculty Meetings IV, 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Faculty Meetings V, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Faculty Meetings VI, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Faculty Meetings VII, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Faculty Meetings IX, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Faculty Meetings X, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Faculty Meetings XI, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Faculty Meetings XII, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Faculty Meetings XIII, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Faculty Meetings XIV, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Faculty Meetings XV, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Faculty Meetings XVI, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Faculty Meetings XVII, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Date Books (1960-1984) (Box 45)
- Faculty Meetings XVIII, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Faculty Meetings XIX, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- University of California, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - Summer '59 Employment, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Johns Hopkins, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- IMS Stanford Meetings, 1960 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Biomathematics Conference (August 1961) (Box 46, Folder 7)
- IMS Seattle Meetings, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Public Health Association, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- IMS Regional Meeting - University of Oregon, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Renovascular Hypertension - Los Angeles, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Thyroid Disease - Utah P.H.S. (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Thyroid Disease - Utah P.H.S. (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- 5th Berkeley Symposium, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Biometry Training Directors Meeting - Chicago, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- IMS Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Office Memos, 1984-1985 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Application for the Continuation of a Public Health Service Grant, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- NIH Research Grant Projects (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Committee on National Statistics I, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Committee on National Statistics II, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- CNSTAT- Travel, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- National Research Council - Statistics of Skin Cancer Research, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- CNSTAT- Skin Cancer, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- CNSAT - EPA, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- EPA Project Documents, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- CNSAT - EPA Project, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- EPA Panel and Staff, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- "Considerations in Spectral Analysis: Comments" by Jenkins and Parzen, 1961 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- National Research Council Report: "Setting Statistical Priorities", 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- EPA Research Methodology Handbooks (Box 49, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences Joint Meeting Folder, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Committee on National Statistics Conference Folder, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- JASA - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Table of Contents, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- JASA - Reports, Memos, 1968-1972 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- JASA - Joint Editorship, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- JASA - Reimbursements, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Annals of Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Annals of Statistics - Monthly Reports, 1977-1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Annals of Statistics - Reports on Savage Manuscripts, 1977-1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Annals of Statistics - Important Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Reprints (1 of 2), 1963-1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Reprints (2 of 2), 1963-1980 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- "Beyond Anova" - Working Copy of Preface and Chapters (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Missouri (Spring 1968) (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Alumni Conference (May 1968) (Box 51, Folder 2)
- NSF Postdoctoral Fellowship Panel (January 1970) (Box 51, Folder 3)
- 6th Berkeley Symposium (Summer 1970) (Box 51, Folder 4)
- ASA Nominating Committee (1970) (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Oregon State (Spring 1971) (Box 51, Folder 6)
- NSF Postdoctoral Fellowship Panel (January 1971) (Box 51, Folder 7)
- NIH Cleveland (January 1972) (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Babette's Party (June 2, 1972) (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Simultaneous Statistical Inference Lectures - LSH & TM (January 1973) (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Claremont Colleges (February 1974) (Box 51, Folder 11)
- NIH Site Visits - Chicago, Seattle ( May 27-29, 1974) (Box 51, Folder 12)
- "A Two Sample Sequential Wilcoxon Test", 1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- "Spurious Appearance of Mosaicism in Three Generations in One Family With a 3/B Translocation" by Miller and Brown, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- "Least Squares Regression with Censored Data", 1974 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- "Probability of Developing Coronary Heart Disease" by Brittain, 1980 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- "Covariance Analysis of Heart Transplant Survival Data" by Crowley and Hu, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- "The Influence Function in the Errors in Variables Problem" by Kelly, 1981 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- "Biostatistics Case Book, Volume One" by Brown, Efron, Hyde, Leurans, Miller, Moses, Wolfe, & Wong (2 copies), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- "Biostatistics Case Book, Volume Two" by Brown, Efron, Hu, Hyde, Leurgans, & Miller (2 copies), 1978 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- "Biostatistics Case Book, Volume Three" by Berry, Brown, Faith, Gale, Gong, Halpern, Leurgans, Miller, & Moses, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- "Survival Analysis" by Miller, Gong, & Munoz (2 copies), 1980 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- "Growth Kinetics of Glioma Cells" by Miller, Halks-Miller, Egger, & Halpern, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- "Probability of Developing Coronary Heart Disease" by Brittain, 1980 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- "Annotated Biostatistics Bibliography" by Brown, Efron, Miller, & Moses, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- NSF Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Postdoctoral Energy-Related Fellowships Packet, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- NAS-NRC: Biomedical Research in Veterans Administration, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- California State University, Hayward Talk, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- ASA - Boston, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- NIEHS Special Study Section, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- 23rd Conference on the Design of Experiments in Army Research, Development, and Testing Packet, 1977 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- ASA Talk - San Francisco, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Army Conference - Monterey, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Berkeley State Department Evaluation, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Mathematics and Science Program Review Committee, 1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- FDA Lectures: Multiple Comparisons, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill Talk, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Internal Evaluation Report on Graduate Degree Programs, University of North Carolina, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Washington, D.C. Meetings, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Robustness Lectures, 1979 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Ad Hoc Panel for Distribution Requirements, 1979-1980 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Sabbatical Leave, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Guest Lecture - UC Davis, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Guest Lecture - UCSF, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Institute for Population Studies (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Editorial Search Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- NIH Special Study Section - Baltimore, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- NIH Special Review Committee - Cedars Sinai, Los Angeles, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- NIH - Arlington, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- IMS Memorials Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Visiting Committee - Harvard, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Subcommittee on Distribution Requirements, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Marie Shou-Jen Hu v. Stanford University Trial, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Matthay - ARDS, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Murray - Pulmonary Edema, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- SRI-EPA, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Morris-LDS, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Schreuder - Rocky Mountain, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Thaler- New York (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Goldman- Los Alamos, 1981 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Ebon Research Systems Packet, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Southern Pacific, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Rockwell, 1978-1980 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Albert Morris - Genesys, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Nickerson- Fractional Report (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Ken Wilson - I.E., 1971 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Jeff Royer - Neuron Model, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- Neighborhood Legal Assistance, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Peter Lawrence - Air Traffic, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- M. Davis - Ionospheric Disturbances, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 23)
- Durkett - Physical Fitness, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Byron Athan - Santa Clara Tax Case, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 25)
- R. Levy - correspondence re programs in Police Records project, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Harris Book, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Point Mugu, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Loring - Leaf Lesions (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Deemer-Thomas Problem, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation Employment Agreement, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Farichild Semiconductor Corporation Report I, 1959 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation Report II, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Fairchild Materials (1 of 2), 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Fairchild Materials (2 of 2), 1959-1961 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Bond - Signal Corps, 1956 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Wilson - Education (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Holden-Day Book Reviews, 1967-1974 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- McGraw-Hill Book Reviews, 1966-1968 (Box 55, Folder 14)
- Havcourt, Brace, and World Book Reviews, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- Houghton Mifflin Book Reviews, 1960 (Box 55, Folder 16)
- Wiley Book Reviews, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 17)
- Prentice-Hall Book Reviews, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 18)
- Wadsworth International Group, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 19)
- Springer-Verlag Publishers, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 20)
- Wiley Series, 1981-1985 (Box 55, Folder 21)
- Wiley: Buja-Stuetzle, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 22)
- Wiley: Persi, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 23)
- Wiley: Ghosh, Sen, and Mukhopadhyay, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 24)
- Wiley: Feigl/Wahl, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 25)
- Wiley: Goldberg-Wittes, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Wiley: Fleiss, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Wiley: Govindarajulu, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- Wiley: Freeman, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- Wiley: Gross, Clark, Elashoff, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Wiley: Gaver-Lehoczky, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Wiley: Hettmansperger, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- Wiley: Hwang-Sobel, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- Wiley: Jureckova-Sen, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Wiley: Kaufman-Rousseeuw, 1982 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- Wiley: Selvin/Sacks, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 11)
- Wiley: Searle, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 12)
- Wiley: Woolson-Tsuang, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 13)
- Manual of Operations for Extracorporeal Suopport for Respiratory Insufficiency, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- "Computer Information" by Maureen Clarke, 1974-1975 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- National Heart and Lung Institute Protocols for Extracorporeal Support for Respiratory Insufficiency, 1974-1975 (Box 56, Folder 16)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare Request for Proposal: RFP-NHLI-75-6, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 17)
- ECMO Collaborative Study Data Center Annual Report, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 18)
- ECMO Collaborative Study - Statistical Coordinating Center Report, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 19)
- ECMO Collaborative Study -Membrance Oxygenator Clinical Program Binder, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 20)
- Extracorporeal Support for Respiratory Insufficiency - A Randomized Clinical Trial, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Summary of Analysis of Additional Data Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Characteristics of Trimmed ECMO and Control Groups - All Outcomes, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- ECMO Collaborative Study - Summary of Raw Data for Primary and Secondary Diagnoses and Causes of Death, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Report Number: HR-42923-F - Extracorporeal Support for Respiratory Insufficiency, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Report Number: NO1-HR-42915-42922 - Extracorporeal Support for Respiratory Insufficiency, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- ECMO Data Center Program Documentation, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- ECMO Collaborative Study Data Center Summary - Years One and Two, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- ECMO Collaborative Study Data Center Summary for Years One and Two - Volume 2 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- "Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenation in Severe Acute Respiratory Failure: A Randomized Prospective Study", 1979 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Summary Statistics Final Report - ECMO Data Center, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Handouts - San Francisco Meeting - ECMO, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- ECMO Documents, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- ECMO Literature, 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Clinical Trial Literature (General), 1969-1973 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- ECMO Studies, 1970-1977 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- ECMO Travel, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- ECMO Accounts, 1974-1978 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- ECMO Communications, 1977-1983 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- ECMO Communications I, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- ECMO Communications II, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- ECMO Communications III, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- ECMO Communications IV, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Folder 6)
- Stanford Statistics (Folder 7)
- Sherrie Emoto, 1982-1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- J. Halpern, 1982-1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Carol Link - Survival Estimates with Covariates, 1978-1979 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- John Orar, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Joe Marhoul, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Chen, Chen-Hsin, 1972-1981 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Kelly, Gabrielle, 1977-1984 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Nancy Reid, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- J. Hyde - Martongales & Censored Data, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Jean Sander Chmiel - Kaplan-Meier Median, 1974-1976 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- F. Guiahi (1 of 2), 1973-1979 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- F. Guiahi (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 5)
- O. Whitby - Beta Distribution, 1969-1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- K. Lamborn - Inverse Regression (Box 61, Folder 7)
- K. Lamborn - X ^ 2 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- L. Weldon -Final Draft, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- L. Weldon - Second Draft, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- L. Weldon - First Draft, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- L. Weldon - Working Papers, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- M. Layard - Robust Covariance, 1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- J. Averson - Jackknife Components of Variance, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- M. Hamilton - Robbins-Monroe Discrimination, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Paul Holmes Thesis, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- J. Thiebaux - Markov Chain Inference for DNA, 1957-1964 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- H. Weiner - Semi-Markov Branching Processes, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- B. Efron - Thesis, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Simulatneous Correlation (Box 62, Folder 9)
- WALD - Vision, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Willett - Dissertation, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- J. Halpern - Small Sample Max X^2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Erica Brittain - Coronary Risk, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Alvaro Munoz, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Pat Morissey, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Keaven Anderson - Thesis Project (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Buckley Thesis, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Marlene Egger, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Sue Leurgans (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Linda Flanders - Conformity Models, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Duan - Median Permutation Test, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Bob Wolfe, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- M. Wesley - Bayesian Bioassay, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- J. Chmiel - Spearmar Var Estimator, 1974-1977 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- T. O'Neill Thesis (Box 64, Folder 7)
- H. Braun (Box 64, Folder 8)
- McKay, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Matubara, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Shapiro (Box 64, Folder 11)
- J. Reading Thesis, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Sheffield Oral Exam - Niels Becker, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- A. Mallik (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Reprints, 1956-1985 (Box 65)
- Video-taped lectures from Stat 116, 9/29/82-10/15/82, 1982; 3/4 inch video cassettes (Box 66)
- Video-taped lectures from Stat 116, 10/18/82-11/9/82, 3/4 inch video cassettes (Box 67)
- Video-taped lectures from Stat 116, 11/10/82-12/10/82, 1982; 3/4 inch video cassettes (Box 68)